Debjeet Banerjee

38, Path Bari Lane, Panihati, Sodepur, Kol-114 (+91) 91639 80758

whokilleddb@protonmail.com

Github O LinkedIn Twitter

Cyber Security professional with 2+ years of experience. Skilled in web application penetration testing, application security, binary exploitation, and network penetration testing. Currently focused on securing Open Source Software, while pursuing my Bachelor's in Technology (CS).

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

PAYATU Pune, India

Security Consultant Intern

February 2022-Present

- Perform comprehensive web application and network penetration tests for clients along with comprehensive reporting on the same
- Design challenges for Capture the Flag events
- Write educational blogs on various security related topics

CYBERPWN TECHNOLOGIES

BANGALORE, INDIA

Security Analyst Intern

Nov 2021–Jan 2022

- Carry out penetration testing activities across client web applications and networks to identify vulnerabilities and bugs in the application.
- Perform configuration reviews and static code analysis
- Develop automation scripts to enhance offensive security capabilities and provide hands-on training to development teams on secure code practices

CYBERFRAT MUMBAI, INDIA

Technical Project Intern

June 2021-August 2021

- Design enterprise security posture and architecture
- Set up proper access management integration
- Setup endpoint management systems like UEM, EMM and MDM
- Compare services across various vendors to bring forth the most optimal solutions for clients

CERTIFICATIONS

- Junior Penetration Tester | eLearnSecurity
- Red Team Operator Malware Development Essentials | Sektor7
- **CNSS Certified Network Security Specialist | ICSI**
- Splunk 7.x Fundamentals Part -1
- **Splunk User Behavior Analytics**
- **Network Protocols and Architecture | CISCO**
- Introduction to Cybersecurity | NYU

PUBLISHED CVE(s)

- CVE-2022-0845: Code Injection in GitHub repository pytorchlightning/pytorch-lightning prior to 1.6.0.
- CVE-2021-42192: Konga v0.14.9 is affected by a privilege escalation vulnerability.
- CVE-2022-2054: Command Injection in GitHub repository nuitka/nuitka prior to 0.9.

PROJECTS

- <u>1s0lat3</u>: A Linux sandbox written from scratch using **C** which uses **Namespaces** to create a docker-like containerised environment.
- Follina: A PoC Exploit for CVE-2022-30190: "Follina"
- Smoochum: A LD_PRELOAD based rootkit inspired directly by the infamous Jynx Rootkit
- <u>Fake Stream</u>: Use **v4l2loopback** kernel modules and **ffmpeg** to create a shell script which takes a video as input and streams it on loop as your webcam output.
- <u>LazarusOS</u>: A **Rust-based** operating system written entirely from scratch.
- <u>Weaponizing OpenWRT</u>: Turn a **TP-MR3020** Router into a Linux computer with networking tools cross compiled for **MIPS** architecture.
- Multiple Exploits for popular 0-day and N-Day Vulnerabilities

MENTORING/VOLUNTEERING

- Security Researcher at IEM IEDC
- Cyber Security chapter lead with GDSC, CC, ACM
- Winter of Code Mentor 2020
- Mentor with Smile India Foundation

OTHER FOSS CONTRIBUTIONS

- Contributed to security tools like Metasploit and Social Engineering Toolkit
- Contributor at **OWASP Pygoat**
- Fixed Security vulnerabilities in **Pytorch-lightning**
- Fix security vulnerabilities in **CommaAI**, **flairNLP**, **etc**.

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Python

• C

- Bash

ASM

Rust

Javascript

EDUCATION

INSTITUTE OF ENGINEERING AND MANAGEMENT

Bachelor of Technology(CS),

CGPA: 9.63

ST XAVIER'S INSTITUTION

ISC Examination,

Percentage of Marks: 97.25%